So let's get started with this course.
Zacznijmy od tego kursu.
But first, I want to explain to you how you can get the most out of this course.
Ale najpierw chciabym ci wyjani, jak moesz w peni wykorzysta ten kurs.
Obviously, you'll watch the videos and I highly recommend that you also code along; write
Oczywicie, obejrzysz filmy i bardzo polecam, aby take kodowa razem; napisz
the code yourself.
kod sam.
This is how you'll learn the most.
W ten sposb nauczysz si najbardziej.
Additionally, check my source code
Dodatkowo sprawd mj kod
if you're encountering issues. You can find it attached to the end of each module and also to a lot
rdowy, jeli napotykasz problemy. Moesz go znale na kocu kadego moduu,
of lectures throughout the module. I provide the source code because sometimes it's just a tiny typo
a take na wielu wykadach w caym module. Dostarczam kod rdowy, poniewa czasami jest to po prostu drobna literwka,
and if you then run my source code and compare it to yours, you will be able to find out what's wrong
a jeli uruchomisz mj kod rdowy i porwnasz go ze swoim, bdziesz w stanie dowiedzie si,
in your code and get a deeper understanding of why it went wrong.
co jest nie tak w kodzie i lepiej zrozumie, dlaczego co poszo nie tak.
Also, consider the many hints and things
Rozwa take wiele wskazwek i rzeczy, ktrych
I will teach you in the debugging section of this course.
naucz ci w sekcji debugowania tego kursu.
There, I will teach you how to handle React errors and how to react to them and fix them;
Tam naucz ci obsugiwa bdy React i jak na nie reagowa i naprawia je; zdecydowanie
definitely something you have to know how to do.
co, co musisz wiedzie, jak to zrobi.
So use that knowledge you gain there to fix any issues you encounter.
Wykorzystaj zdobyt wiedz, aby naprawi wszelkie napotkane problemy.
Now, if you're stuck and you can't find the error, ask in the Q&A section.
Jeli utkniesz i nie moesz znale bdu, zapytaj w sekcji Pytania i odpowiedzi.
My team and I are more than happy to help you. But, this is important,
Mj zesp i ja z przyjemnoci Ci pomoemy. Ale to jest wane, nie
don't just ask but
tylko pytaj, ale take
also answer in the Q&A.
odpowiedz w pytaniach i odpowiedziach.
I'm not saying this because I don't want to answer your questions.
Nie mwi tego, poniewa nie chc odpowiada na twoje pytania.
I will, but if you answer, you'll learn way more than if you just ask.
Bd, ale jeli odpowiesz, nauczysz si duo wicej, ni po prostu zapytasz.
Asking is super-simple; but answering is hard.
Pytanie jest super proste; ale odpowiadanie jest trudne.
You can't go wrong and
Nie moesz si pomyli i nawet
even if your answer is wrong, no one is going to kill you.
jeli twoja odpowied jest za, nikt ci nie zabije.
Instead, you're going to learn if people correct you and answering forces you to think about a problem
Zamiast tego dowiesz si, czy ludzie ci poprawi, a odpowied sprawi, e bdziesz musia pomyle o problemie
and find a solution.
i znale rozwizanie.
If you really want to become a great React developer, you have to solve problems and answering the Q&A
Jeli naprawd chcesz zosta wietnym programist React, musisz rozwizywa problemy, a odpowiadanie na pytania
section is a good way of practicing just that. Finally, practice, practice, practice;
i odpowiedzi to dobry sposb na praktyk. Wreszcie, wicz, wicz, wicz; to
it's as easy as that.
takie proste.
Even after you've finished this course, you've got to practice the things you've learned.
Nawet po ukoczeniu tego kursu musisz wiczy to, czego si nauczye.
You have to build your own demo projects, set your own challenges, do the exercises from this course, alter
Musisz zbudowa wasne projekty demonstracyjne, ustawi wasne wyzwania, wykona wiczenia z tego kursu, zmieni kod, ktrego
the code you'll learn in this course and practice React.
nauczysz si w tym kursie i wiczy React.
If you follow these steps and follow through this entire course, you'll be an awesome React developer
Jeli wykonasz te kroki i przejdziesz przez cay kurs, bdziesz wietnym programist React i bdziesz
and you'll be able to apply for jobs,
mg ubiega si o prac,
become a React freelancer; whatever you want. With that,
zosta freelancerem React; cokolwiek chcesz. Dziki temu zagbimy si
let's dive into React and learn how it works.
w React i nauczymy si, jak to dziaa.